<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
    <title>AnonJr.com</title>
    <link>https://www.anonjr.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.anonjr.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 15:14:39 -04:00</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 15:14:39 -04:00</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Didn&apos;t Post This</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-Didnt-Post-This.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-Didnt-Post-This.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No big long deep thoughts today either - a very tiring day at work left me drained. So here&apos;s a brief &amp;quot;thinking out loud&amp;quot; kind of thing, slightly related to &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Deep-Thougths-Coming-Soon.html&quot;&gt;yesterday&apos;s riff&lt;/a&gt;. I almost didn&apos;t post, but I didn&apos;t want to break the forward momentum on actually writing and posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m sure someone will point to this as a counterpoint to &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/In-Defence-of-Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;my defense&lt;/a&gt; of writing a post a day, use it as an example of the low-quality, low-energy post of dubious value that is better relegated to the &amp;quot;drafts&amp;quot; bin. And on the one hand, they&apos;d be right. I truly hope they never know what it&apos;s like struggling with burnout and some of the concerns I raised in &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html&quot;&gt;Sabbaticals, Reflections, and Changes&lt;/a&gt;. It&apos;s for those struggling that I post - you too can persevere, post and progress, no matter what that little negative voice in the back of your head is saying. For that matter, this very post was little more than the first sentence and the next paragraph until I actually sat down and started writing. That&apos;s probably a thought worth further examination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, back to the original spark: I&apos;m wondering if I&apos;m striking the right balance between &amp;quot;good enough&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;minimally acceptable&amp;quot; in a couple of projects. Two of the bigger concerns are CoffeeCraft and Bible By Example. (See &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&quot;&gt;Projects Projects Projects&lt;/a&gt; for the Cliff Notes version)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think tomorrow I&apos;ll do a status update on one, Friday the other, and revisit this idea on Saturday. Look at that, a plan. Yesterday and today may have been low-energy days, but tomorrow&apos;s a new day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Thoughts Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Deep-Thougths-Coming-Soon.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Deep-Thougths-Coming-Soon.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No big long deep thoughts today… got kinda wrapped up in having a day off. As more of a &amp;quot;thinking out loud&amp;quot; kind of thing, one of the ideas I&apos;ve had bouncing around has to do with the balance between &amp;quot;good enough&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;minimally acceptable&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things I heard a lot while working at the hospital was &amp;quot;don&apos;t make perfect the enemy of good&amp;quot;. While that&apos;s a wonderful sentiment, and true as most truisms go, it does still manage to miss the point - where&apos;s &amp;quot;good&amp;quot;? Usually it was said while trying to raise the online education up to some minimally reasonable standard as recognized by multiple experts in the field, or at least that&apos;s how I saw it. They saw it as some sort of perfectionist streak run wild. While I&apos;ll admit I have such a streak, I&apos;m usually self-aware enough to see when it&apos;s kicking in and compensate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suspect the problem is the same as one I&apos;m seeing elsewhere now - &amp;quot;it was good enough before, so it should be good enough now&amp;quot;. They only saw the online education through the lens of what had come before, and in that context what I was trying to implement was far above what had come before (though very much a baby step in getting the training in line with more current standards). Having said all that, I now see that we were far and away better than the training some other companies are pushing on their employees… but that&apos;s another topic for another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know there&apos;s a way to tie these two things together, and with more illustrative examples. That&apos;s the thought exercise for the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defence of Almost NaNoWriMo</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/In-Defence-of-Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/In-Defence-of-Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not 1/6&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of the way in to &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;Almost NaNoWriMo&lt;/a&gt;, and I&apos;ll admit to feeling a little defensive. I was originally thinking of this article this morning in terms of being a spot-check or reflection on the exercise so far, but if I&apos;m being brutally honest, it was a couple of comments that have been on a slow burn in the back of my mind since last night:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-05-UnhelpfulAdvice-01.png&quot; title=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-05-UnhelpfulAdvice-02.png&quot; title=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now please don&apos;t hear what I&apos;m not saying: I&apos;m not judging the &lt;em&gt;intent&lt;/em&gt; of the commenter, just the &lt;em&gt;approach&lt;/em&gt; and the &lt;em&gt;potential results&lt;/em&gt;. On the latter part, I won&apos;t pretend to speak for anyone else - I lost a bit of the fire and enthusiasm gained from starting the endevour, finding some &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/mark_nicol/an-article-a-day-for-november-41f5&quot;&gt;kindred&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/lvrbrtsn/article-a-day-375h&quot;&gt;spirits&lt;/a&gt;, and seeing the encouraging comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first commenter I certainly understand the sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody has an enlightening though or experience every day. This would be a great source of spam. Please don&apos;t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been around the internet for a while. I&apos;ve got a twitter account. I&apos;m fully aware of what daily, &lt;em&gt;thoughtless&lt;/em&gt; posting can produce and wholeheartedly would not encourage more of the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d also argue that it&apos;s not impossible to live a life well examined. A life where every day holds one or more new bits of information, new insights on existing information, and/or new perspectives. Many of those could be shared in short or long form in a challenge like this. For that matter, I could easily see someone grabbing one of the daily writer&apos;s posts and using them as a launchpad for counterpoints, expansion, or something more tangential. For that matter, I&apos;ve written more than a few comments over the years that really could have been the launching point for a blog post (if not a post in and of themselves… I&apos;ve gotten long-winded from time to time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Same for the second commenter, I get what they mean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt; articles, not &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; articles. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quality usually does trump quantity, and we&apos;d all love to see our favorite places filled with &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt; articles, not &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; articles. I&apos;ve left some of my favorite sites because they cranked up the quantity for one reason or another, and in the process the quality level plummeted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The part that would be easy to miss though is that you can&apos;t get to &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt; articles without going through &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; articles; or at least more articles with a particular mindset and approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I closed out the first post in this series with an analogy, and now might be a good time to put a little context into that analogy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quite frankly I feel like an athlete who&apos;s been on a long recovery finally getting back into training. Now that I think about it, that&apos;s probably a more apt analogy than I&apos;m ready to admit to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of what makes that analogy apt is I&apos;ve gone through some fitness roller-coasters - periods of varying length where I worked out regularly and was in great physical shape, and periods where I was … well, not. I&apos;ve also helped others through similar periods. In college, I worked in the Aquatics department at the local YMCA where (among other jobs) I taught swim lessons and was the assistant coach for some elementary, junior, and senior high school swim teams (I was licensed as an ASCA Level 2 coach for the curious).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the athletic space we recognize a few things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The old saw &amp;quot;practice makes perfect&amp;quot; is missing a few words - &amp;quot;practice makes &lt;em&gt;permanent&lt;/em&gt;; perfect practice makes perfect&amp;quot;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don&apos;t get to a &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt; 5k without doing &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; 5k&apos;s. (Longest swim I ever did. There&apos;s a story there.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also recognize this in the programming space, where we understand that growth requires working on projects, exercises, and using various training programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to the writing - you don&apos;t get to &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt; articles without writing &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; articles; or at least more articles with a particular mindset and approach. We can see this in some of the more helpful comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-05-SemihelpfulAdvice-01.png&quot; title=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s going to take deliberate, focused steps to get the quality where it needs to be. For me, the first few have been a matter of showing up. It&apos;s hard to improve if you&apos;re not showing up. This is something that &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/lvrbrtsn/on-staying-motivated--4861&quot;&gt;others&lt;/a&gt; doing the &amp;quot;November Daily&amp;quot; thing have pointed to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post and the next few are going to be posts that I&apos;ve spent a little more time setting up and figuring out what I want to articulate. I&apos;m also going to keep an eye on the reading ease and other statistics &lt;a href=&quot;https://wereturtle.github.io/ghostwriter/&quot;&gt;Ghostwriter&lt;/a&gt; provides. For the moment I&apos;m not going to do much with them, just look at what I&apos;m actually doing, so I&apos;ll know where I need to go from there. My target will be a 10&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; grade reading level. It&apos;s a little higher than the usual recommendation, but is a step better than what I&apos;ve managed with this post. (I&apos;ll put a screenshot at the end)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having done &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&quot;&gt;Projects Projects Projects&lt;/a&gt;, I&apos;ve got a good idea of what I really want to do something with (or at least what in the near future I want to focus on), and from there I can build a more structured schedule. Probably won&apos;t happen by the next post or two, but it should be in place before the end of the week. I&apos;ve got to put the car in the shop which should leave me plenty of time to walk over to the coffee shop and think. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and for those wondering, here&apos;s the statistics for this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-05-WritingStats-01.png&quot; title=&quot;Ghostwriter&apos;s Document Statistics&quot; alt=&quot;Ghostwriter&apos;s Document Statistics&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
Ghostwriter&apos;s Document Statistics
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Feed for Dev.to</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in January 2017 I started following what looked like a small and promising community of programmers (and those in adjacent fields) over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt;. At the time I had the site&apos;s whole feed pumping into my Feedly list, I&apos;d commented on a few posts, and I was starting to think about either revitalizing this blog or picking some other platform for posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end I decided to try and revitalize this site, beginning with &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html&quot;&gt;a bit on the tech&lt;/a&gt; behind a couple of projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things I&apos;d considered at the time, and mentioned in &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&quot;&gt;Projects Projects Projects&lt;/a&gt;, is setting up a custom RSS feed for just the articles I wanted to submit at Dev.To. I plan on publishing a wide variety of articles here, and I know not all of them will be right for the community there, so I want to make sure I&apos;m filtering out the rest. I tried just running my regular RSS feed to my profile there, but it left a lot of cruft on my dashboard in the &lt;em&gt;drafts&lt;/em&gt;, and even if I deleted the drafts they would just show up again on the next refresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to this bit - I&apos;ve got a second RSS feed now with just the articles that I want to send over there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the front matter I have a &lt;code&gt;repost&lt;/code&gt; variable like so:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-04-frontmatter.png&quot; title=&quot;(side note: need to fix the highlighting/rendering of markdown code in posts...)&quot; alt=&quot;(side note: need to fix the highlighting/rendering of markdown code in posts...)&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
(side note: need to fix the highlighting/rendering of markdown code in posts...)
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally I was going to set up a &amp;quot;to-dev.to&amp;quot; tag, and go that way, but that didn&apos;t seem useful for the people who were visiting my site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there&apos;s now a &lt;code&gt;todev.to.xml&lt;/code&gt; that filters through the posts for just those that I want to republish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-04-devtoxml.png&quot; title=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At my next opportunity, I&apos;m going to try and pump it through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/penibelst/jekyll-compress-html&quot;&gt;Compress layout&lt;/a&gt; and see if that can get the size down without breaking anything. Though now that I think about it, I&apos;d have to either adapt it to work with &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Code52/pretzel&quot;&gt;Pretzel&lt;/a&gt; or do the Pretzel-to-Jekyll conversion first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there&apos;s the short version. I&apos;m sure there&apos;s a more efficient way to do this, but I probably won&apos;t worry too much about it until I do the conversion to Jekyll. I don&apos;t plan on adding any more features before then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Hot damn! that makes 4 for 4 on my &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;Almost NaNoWriMo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;!)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sabbaticals, Reflections, and Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve had a few versions of this post floating around for longer than I care to think about. What follows is something closer to what I&apos;d started around the same time I was working on the &amp;quot;13 Years in the Valley&amp;quot; retrospectives. For some reason I thought I&apos;d more directly stated just how bad the burnout was, but after looking back I apparently only had the conversation as fully and expressedly in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let&apos;s start the &lt;em&gt;reflection&lt;/em&gt; part of this endevour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burnout is one of those things that&apos;s been written about a lot lately, particularly in the tech industry. If you&apos;re not familiar, the Wikipedia page on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Occupational_burnout&quot;&gt;Occupational Burnout&lt;/a&gt; is a good overview of the subject. &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt; also has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/mary_grace/burnout-what-happens-when-you-take-on-too-much-74d&quot;&gt;couple&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/wolfemurray/burnout-8hk&quot;&gt;articles&lt;/a&gt; worth reading. While I&apos;ve not quite hit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.popehat.com/2015/05/21/happy-to-be-here/&quot;&gt;Happy to be Here&lt;/a&gt; territory, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thebloggess.com/furiously-happy/&quot;&gt;Furiously Happy&lt;/a&gt; certainly had some chapters that resonated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I&apos;m being completely honest, the warning signs were there in 2014. I may even get to some of that in a resumed rendition of retrospectives. In January 2016 I reached a point where I was at least willing to admit something was deeply wrong and find out just where I was at. So I took the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maslach_Burnout_Inventory&quot;&gt;Maslach Burnout Inventory&lt;/a&gt; and found the following results looking back at me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-03-MBIResults.png&quot; title=&quot;&amp;hellip;ouch.&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;hellip;ouch.&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&amp;hellip;ouch.
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to work within the system, I tried counseling, and in the end it just wasn&apos;t getting better. In an ideal world I would have taken more regular time off, and I would have advocated for a more balanced life for myself, and recognized when the work environment was no longer healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That would have been good then, so what to do now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember a long time ago reading about how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.joelonsoftware.com/2000/03/18/more-on-sabbaticals/&quot;&gt;we should all take sabbaticals&lt;/a&gt;. At the time I read Joel&apos;s post I didn&apos;t really take it to heart. I&apos;d just finished college, and was still only months into my brand new job. The idea that I could be so tired and run down that an extended time away was needed … I just couldn&apos;t comprehend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I get it. &lt;em&gt;Time to take a sabbatical.&lt;/em&gt; December 15, 2017 I stepped down from full-time work and moved to a per-diem teaching position. The end of 14 years full-time work at Cape Fear Valley. Teaching was a nice way to keep up professionally, and get myself out of the house from time to time. Unfortunately, it was also still too much. So in June I quit completely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get ready for the sabbatical, in September 2017 I started working part-time at the local Music and Arts. I added the earnings to my current savings and pumped up what I was terming my &amp;quot;sabbatical fund&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing that given my energy levels were what they were, I kept the job to make sure I&apos;d get out of the house and actually engage in the time honored tradition of verbal communication with actual humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-03_JabbaRelaxing.jpg&quot; title=&quot;Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.&quot; alt=&quot;Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where the &lt;em&gt;changes&lt;/em&gt; part was supposed to go, but I&apos;ve run out of steam. Definitely to be finished before the month is up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Projects Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;yesterday&apos;s post&lt;/a&gt; I mentioned my goals for the coming month, and one was going through the various projects and giving a bit of a status report on them. Today&apos;s going to be a bit of a high-level overview, and the next few posts will dig a little deeper into each project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In no particular order, here we go:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;coffeecraft.us&quot;&gt;CoffeeCraft.us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project is at the forefront of my mind - in no small part because it&apos;s one of the most recent to be started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve got a small survival Minecraft server going at home that my sister, her husband, and I have been playing on. Inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;http://hermitcraft.com/&quot;&gt;HermitCraft&lt;/a&gt;, we&apos;ve fired up a fresh world for &amp;quot;Season 00&amp;quot; so we can get used to working together in a way that works better for making videos and live streaming - which we all plan on starting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The domain registered, I&apos;ve started in on building the website, and there&apos;s a few other bits in the works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;bible-by-example&quot;&gt;Bible By Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a bible study podcast that I&apos;ve been working on off-and-on for nearly a year. It&apos;s  been long past time to get this in gear&amp;amp;helip; A decent enough first run of the website is together, and I&apos;m not entirely sure what&apos;s left to do to be ready to launch. Getting a handle on this will definitely be a part of this month&apos;s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;anonjr.com&quot;&gt;AnonJr.com&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yup, this site. I&apos;ve got a few things planned - from migrating from Pretzel to Jekyl, to getting a dedicated feed for the articles I want to republish on &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt;. I&apos;d also like to tighten up some style/design bits while I&apos;m at it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The end goal is to make this the central hub for everything I&apos;m doing, and having various tags for the individual projects or subjects for those that don&apos;t want &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;wayward-son-developers&quot;&gt;Wayward Son Developers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a site I&apos;d put together long ago when I&apos;d started building sites for some friends and acquaintances, and I figured I&apos;d rather do it under a &amp;quot;company&amp;quot; than under my own name. At the time was considering doing some contract site building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If nothing else, I&apos;d like to get it to the place where it serves two purposes: a showcase of what I can do for prospective employers, and a home for my programming related posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;d20-project&quot;&gt;D20 Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an older project that I&apos;d started somewhere in 2014-ish and stalled out. Basically while playing a D&amp;amp;D campaign set in Eberron, I started wondering what it would look like if the traditional D&amp;amp;D setting had grown to a more modern-like world (as opposed to stalling in a Renaissance-esque world like Eberron). So I started working on a campaign setting with my sister and her husband to build just that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan was to build on top of the OGL 3.5e material, and maybe make some tweaks to fit the world we were building and fix a few gripes we&apos;d all had at our various settings. We had some basic character building done, and were starting in on the next steps when everything kinda stalled out. Long story for another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;asp-ajaxed&quot;&gt;ASP-Ajaxed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right before the burnout started kicking in hard and impacting my ability to function, I&apos;d offered to take over ASP-Ajaxed - a framework for Classic ASP projects. While I&apos;m not doing much Classic ASP work now, and I&apos;m not sure I&apos;m going to continue down that road, I&apos;d like to get a better project site going and tidy up a few things. As it sits now it&apos;s still fairly solid for those poor souls who still need to work with Classic ASP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-other-game-streaming&quot;&gt;Some other game streaming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d like to get at least one or two more game streams going, just because I&apos;d like to diversify my podcasts. I worry that specializing in just Minecraft might leave me hanging if it ever drops in popularity. (though I don&apos;t see that happening for some time)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve considered doing a World of Tanks stream on Saturdays, and calling it &amp;quot;The 48%&amp;quot; (inside joke for the stat obsessed), though I worry that the game is falling and might not be around in any big way in the near future - and more important than that, I just haven&apos;t been having as much fun with the game lately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve also considered doing Fallout or something like it just because I&apos;m a bit of an antisocial gamer. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrapping-it-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping it up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really feel like I&apos;ve forgotten something, but at this hour that&apos;s not surprising. Tomorrow I&apos;ll pick one and do a bit of a deeper look at where it&apos;s at and what needs to happen. From there the goal is to start making actual progress and to focus the posts on status updates and/or do some thinking out loud type stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost NaNoWriMo</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems a little ridiculous to tag this &amp;quot;NaNoWriMo&amp;quot;, but I&apos;m not really sure what to call it. I&apos;ve had a few posts in draft for longer than I care to mention, and while the desire has been there the energy has been lacking… most likely to be the subject of some upcoming posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don&apos;t know, &lt;a href=&quot;https://nanowrimo.org/&quot;&gt;NaNoWriMo&lt;/a&gt; is short for National Novel Writing Month. The idea being that you just start writing at the start of November, and work at a steady pace to have a completed work by the end of the month. Just writing, edit later. It&apos;s a really nice idea for helping those of us who just need a little push to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve gone through the motions of starting a novel a couple of times, and unfortunately never actually followed through. My intent had been to actually participate this year and produce one of the two novels that&apos;s been kicking around in the back of my mind for quite some time. Life being what it&apos;s been, I just wasn&apos;t ready to start and didn&apos;t want to feel behind this early on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So - new objective. Blogging has been another writing activity that I&apos;ve long intended to do, but never seem to actually make happen. For the month of November my goal is to get at least one post out a day. By the end of November I&apos;ll work out a more reasonable posting schedule. The hope is that once I get started, maintaining momentum will be a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for some updates on old projects, some &amp;quot;talking out loud&amp;quot; type planning on upcoming projects, and a few other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quite frankly I feel like an athlete who&apos;s been on a long recovery finally getting back into training. Now that I think about it, that&apos;s probably a more apt analogy than I&apos;m ready to admit to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective: 13 Years in the Valley, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/09/13-Years-In-The-Valley-2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 13:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/09/13-Years-In-The-Valley-2.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot of life has been happening, and it seems maybe I need a little perspective - and so this &amp;quot;retrospective&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Six days later and I still haven&apos;t quite gotten into the habit of regular blogging yet, so whatever is done by the time my lunch break is over is what&apos;s getting posted. Like before, some of that time was taken getting some essentials:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2017-09-14_EssentialAsset.png&quot; title=&quot;Essential Asset&quot; alt=&quot;Essential Asset&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
Essential Asset
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/09/13-Years-In-The-Valley-1.html&quot;&gt;Last time&lt;/a&gt; I went over some background to add a little context to what came next. December 2003, fresh out of college with my brand new 2-year degree, I started working at Cape Fear Valley (CFV) in the Education department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can hear it now – &amp;quot;Education?&amp;quot; – my job was an IT role, but not in the IT (&apos;scuse me, &lt;em&gt;IST&lt;/em&gt; as they prefer) department. Ostensibly, at the time I interviewed and was hired, my role was twofold:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My secondary job was to teach Basic Life Support classes (BLS - basically CPR for the Healthcare worker). Fortunately I&apos;d paid for college by working at the local YMCA as (among other roles) a Lifeguard Instructor. I just needed to switch over my teaching credentials from the Red Cross to the AHA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was made abundantly clear that teaching BLS is one of the things that &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; in the department did. At the time we had 2,500 employees, and a large percentage were required to maintain a current BLS card. A department-wide effort was needed to run the necessary classes to make that happen. It seems so quaint now that we&apos;re trying to do the same for a larger percentage of our now 7,000 employees, and yes it is still a department-wide effort. Fortunately we have a bigger department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My primary job was to maintain the internal online education website – a collection of fliers/class info for our live training (ILT if you want the more formal industry jargon), some online presentations and tests for our online training (eLearning is technically the right term, but at this stage calling what we were doing &amp;quot;eLearning&amp;quot; was a bit of a stretch), and other department-related stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Side note: I&apos;d taken the Advanced Web Programming class on a whim to fill one of the credit requirements. It covered HTML, some very basic JavaScript, and PERL/CGI scripting. When I took it I never thought that that&apos;s the job I&apos;d end up with. Then again, I&apos;d already previously stated that I&apos;d never work in healthcare, I&apos;d never work in education, and I&apos;d never do programming. And there I was programming for the Education department in a health system. Lesson learned: never say never. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site was a hacked together mess of static HTML pages and some PERL scripts (more on that in a minute) running on an NT4 server. I think I still have a zipped copy floating around somewhere… I might have to dig it up and post some screencaps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My predecessor was a Nurse Educator who had been tasked with creating the website. While she was smart, this wasn&apos;t exactly her bailiwick. There was no master CSS, inline styles run amok, no &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- #include --&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; statements to be found (granted, it was hosted on NT4 in 2003, but even NT4 had server-side includes), and the general design and cohesion to rival the best the late ‘90s had to offer (did I mention this was 2003?).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only server scripting was the PERL used to grade the test and record the results. Since lunch is nearly up and I need a minute to publish, I&apos;ll leave that for the starting point of the next part.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective: 13 Years in the Valley, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/09/13-Years-In-The-Valley-1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 13:45:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/09/13-Years-In-The-Valley-1.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot of life has been happening, and it seems maybe I need a little perspective - and so this &amp;quot;retrospective&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-part-1&quot;&gt;Why Part 1?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I haven&apos;t quite gotten into the habit of regular blogging yet, so whatever is done by the time my lunch break is over is what&apos;s getting posted. I&apos;d say lunch hour, but some of that time was taken getting some essentials:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2017-09-14_EssentialAsset.png&quot; title=&quot;Essential Asset&quot; alt=&quot;Essential Asset&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
Essential Asset
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;years-in-the-valley&quot;&gt;13 Years? In the Valley?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started working for Cape Fear Valley Health System back in December 2003, and it&apos;s been quite the wild ride. When I started in 2003 there were two campuses, a few outpatient clinics, and a grand total of 2500 employees. Now? There&apos;s 5-ish campuses, I&apos;ve lost track of how many outpatient clinics, and somewhere in the ballpark of 7000 employees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over that time my roles and responsibilities have grown, creating a somewhat less than tenable position and the aforementioned burnout. I may write about that separately&amp;amp;hellp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;but-first&quot;&gt;But First…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I start going through my time at Cape Fear Valley (henceforth, CFV), I want to make a very important note and a small sidebar on how I even got to CFV since it plays a part in the rest of the story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I go all-in on my experiences, opinions, and whatnot, I want to make clear you shouldn&apos;t put too much stock in the &amp;quot;13 years&amp;quot; part. I know a lot of people will automatically attribute some weight to such lengthy experience - and they &lt;em&gt;shouldn&apos;t&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve seen people with 10 years experience, and I&apos;ve seen people with 1 year experience repeated 10 years in a row - when the big dinner came around they all sat at the same table and got the same cheap pin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which am I? I don&apos;t know any more, probably a mix of the two. As we&apos;ll see, I&apos;ve had periods of growth and periods of stagnation. I&apos;ll leave the ultimate conclusion for the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;howd-i-even-get-here&quot;&gt;How&apos;d I Even get here?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1999 I graduated high school and went to the local community college - it was all I could afford. (There&apos;s a story there too, maybe another time.) I started in the mistaken assumption that since I enjoyed physics and all my science classes, and that since I enjoyed building and fixing things I should get into Engineering. Let&apos;s just say that second semester Calculus class made me re-think things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a series of &amp;amp;hellp; events … I took a semester off. And a year later I started back up again. (Story there too, omitted to cut down on the rabbit trails.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started in the Network Management program, and mostly enjoyed it. I didn&apos;t really get into computers until late-ish in high school. I was (and still am) acutely sensitive to the fact that much of what I learned was whatever I could pick up from whatever was around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About half-way through the program I took the one mandatory &amp;quot;Intro to Programming&amp;quot; course, and it changed things. I was good at it, I loved it, and it fit my desire to build/fix things. I switched majors and finished an Associates degree in Computer Programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my last semester, one of my Prof&apos;s former students was leaving her position at the hospital. She asked him if he had any promising students in mind, and a couple of us went there to interview. Long story short, I interviewed and got the job - starting right after I graduated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts-for-part-1&quot;&gt;Final thoughts for Part 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My hour is almost up, so I&apos;ll close it off here. This has been mostly a as-I-think-of-it deal, and I&apos;m not sure how I feel about working that way. I&apos;m more than a little bit of a perfectionist, but I&apos;ve also gone far too long since the last post - so if this is how it has to happen to get it done, so be it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll probably skip the over-gratuitous headers next time. See you then.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pretzel, A Jekyll, Some Pages, and a Cranky Git</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:00:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t mind the dust, and sorry about the cobwebs… To say it&apos;s been a while would be something of an understatement since the last post is from 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time I was earnestly looking to ramp up and do something with the Blogger account I opened and never actually used for anything other than oAuth. Life hit hard - a combination of events, accumulated effects of a sleep disorder, depression, and the early stages of burnout - and so it sat a little longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve made a few halfhearted attempts to start it all back up, but as you can clearly see nothing came to much. So here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;embedded embedded-youtube&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/Tkfjrp0PNYw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- https://youtu.be/Tkfjrp0PNYw --&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;ve managed to make it this long without watching the awesome (and canceled too soon) show Firefly, get your popcorn and streaming service of choice going and enjoy a weekend binge. We can even compare notes with the good folks at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cordkillers.com/&quot;&gt;Cordkillers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what now? I’m trying to get a few projects lined up:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m almost done rebuilding a few of my websites – this being one of them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m developing a podcast, one I hope to be able to eventually turn into a small income stream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m restarting work on a campaign setting I was building with my sister and her husband.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m (re)starting work on two novels rooted in the above campaign setting. I’d love for both the game and the books to become something awesome and synergistic – I’ll gladly settle for one or the other taking root. I like the world we’re building and I just want to play in it. 😃&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal is to get one or more of these up to enough of an income to cover the bills, and do something different for a while. The various issues creating drag in my life certainly don&apos;t help, but rather than dwell on that let&apos;s look at the actual focus of the title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of my programming work has been in medium-scale CMSs - something that is &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; overkill for a site like this, the podcast site, and a few other projects. So I joined along the static site generator bandwagon and picked a couple to play with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site is using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Code52/pretzel/&quot;&gt;Pretzel&lt;/a&gt;, a .NET tool that&apos;s compatible with the templates and whatnot used by the Ruby-based &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. Since I do most of my work and play on Windows, it seemed like the perfect fit. Especially since (at the time) trying to get Ruby anything running on Windows was a bit of a pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve found a few areas where the templating and Liquid commands don&apos;t &lt;em&gt;quite&lt;/em&gt; fit, but it&apos;s been fairly straight forward. Given my preferences, I do like that Pretzel uses LESS instead of SASS. If there was a little more active development, I&apos;d heartily recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The podcast site (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.biblebyexample.com&quot;&gt;incompletly up&lt;/a&gt; as of writing this) is using the aforementioned Jekyll. When I&apos;d finally mustered enough energy to get cracking on this project, installing Ruby and Jekyll on Windows became significantly less painful. And as long as you&apos;re willing to do a little work with the setup, WSL has made it even easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I managed a little more traction and rapid progress on the latter since I was more willing to grab &lt;a href=&quot;https://mmistakes.github.io/minimal-mistakes/&quot;&gt;a theme that someone else had put together&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both projects are up on GitHub, and are being hosted using GitHub pages. Now that&apos;s been an interesting endevour… particularly getting the domains squared away. The next step for both sites will be to get them behind &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;Cloudflare &lt;/a&gt; for some CDN goodness and HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll write a little more about each project individually, and some &amp;quot;thinking out loud&amp;quot; type posts over the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP-Ajaxed 2.1.1: Finding my feet</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/ASP-Ajaxed-2.1.1_-Finding-my-feet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 09:53:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/ASP-Ajaxed-2.1.1_-Finding-my-feet.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Woot! &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/downloads/detail?name=asp-ajaxed_v2.1.1.zip&quot;&gt;ASP Ajaxed 2.1.1&lt;/a&gt; is up. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned in an &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html&quot;&gt;earlier post&lt;/a&gt;, I took over the ASP Ajaxed project in the hopes of keeping it alive. I&apos;m still orienting myself to how Google Code hosts projects, and I&apos;m still trying to figure out just how I&apos;m going to go about running this particular project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things I found when converting the source control from svn to hg was that there were some bug fixes that were not in the posted 2.1 release. I added a couple of fixes of my own, and a new feature - a SHA256() hashing function - and published &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/downloads/detail?name=asp-ajaxed_v2.1.1.zip&quot;&gt;version 2.1.1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully soon I&apos;ll have a little more about the plans and intentions for this little project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping a good thing going</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 21:53:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do a lot of Classic ASP/VBScript programming - It&apos;s what my bread-winning project is built in, it&apos;s what my side projects are built in, it&apos;s what Snitz Forums (a FLOSS project I help with) is written in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things that has made my life a little easier is a neat little ASP/VBScript framework over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/&quot;&gt;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/&lt;/a&gt;. I&apos;ve integrated it into the LMS I built for work, and a few other work-related projects. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the owner passed away and the project has slowly faded away. Recently the main site disappeared... Not wanting to see a good code base go to waste, I&apos;ve taken ownership of the project (with the blessing of one of the remaining project members).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m not sure where I&apos;m going to begin in getting this thing back up and running, but I do want to keep this project alive and better maintained. Look for more updates to come. 😃&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Projects, New Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/New-Year,-New-Projects,-New-Blog.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 21:42:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>https://www.anonjr.com/2013/06/New-Year,-New-Projects,-New-Blog.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well... the last part is a bit of a stretch. I&apos;ve had this account for quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was recently updating my CV over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://careers.stackoverflow.com/anonjr&quot;&gt;Stack Overflow Careers&lt;/a&gt; and it occurred to me that one thing I&apos;m really short on is publicly available projects and writing... time to fix that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to tell you that I have a plan, and can outline everything this blog will and will not be - but I&apos;d be lying. Waiting until the plan coalesced is why it&apos;s now 2013 and I&apos;m just now posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; tell you that this is not going to have a singular focus. I will most likely have a heavy focus on tech as that&apos;s where I work and play - but I will also write about religion, politics, and maybe a few things of a more personal nature. Jeff Jarvis has often spoke of the therapeutic value of blogging about health issues (and I have a few) so I may throw a few of those out there as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ll see where this goes...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>