<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
    <title>AnonJr.com</title>
    <link>//blog.anonjr.com</link>
    <atom:link href="//blog.anonjr.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:24:23 -04:00</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:24:23 -04:00</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pretzel, A Jekyll, Some Pages, and a Cranky Git</title>
      <link>//blog.anonjr.com/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:00:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>//blog.anonjr.com/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t mind the dust, and sorry about the cobwebs… To say it&apos;s been a while would be something of an understatement since the last post is from 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time I was earnestly looking to ramp up and do something with the Blogger account I opened and never actually used for anything other than oAuth. Life hit hard - a combination of events, accumulated effects of a sleep disorder, depression, and the early stages of burnout - and so it sat a little longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve made a few halfhearted attempts to start it all back up, but as you can clearly see nothing came to much. So here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;embedded embedded-youtube&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/Tkfjrp0PNYw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- https://youtu.be/Tkfjrp0PNYw --&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;ve managed to make it this long without watching the awesome (and canceled too soon) show Firefly, get your popcorn and streaming service of choice going and enjoy a weekend binge. We can even compare notes with the good folks at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cordkillers.com/&quot;&gt;Cordkillers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what now? I’m trying to get a few projects lined up:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m almost done rebuilding a few of my websites – this being one of them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m developing a podcast, one I hope to be able to eventually turn into a small income stream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m restarting work on a campaign setting I was building with my sister and her husband.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m (re)starting work on two novels rooted in the above campaign setting. I’d love for both the game and the books to become something awesome and synergistic – I’ll gladly settle for one or the other taking root. I like the world we’re building and I just want to play in it. 😃&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal is to get one or more of these up to enough of an income to cover the bills, and do something different for a while. The various issues creating drag in my life certainly don&apos;t help, but rather than dwell on that let&apos;s look at the actual focus of the title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of my programming work has been in medium-scale CMSs - something that is &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; overkill for a site like this, the podcast site, and a few other projects. So I joined along the static site generator bandwagon and picked a couple to play with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site is using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Code52/pretzel/&quot;&gt;Pretzel&lt;/a&gt;, a .NET tool that&apos;s compatible with the templates and whatnot used by the Ruby-based &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. Since I do most of my work and play on Windows, it seemed like the perfect fit. Especially since (at the time) trying to get Ruby anything running on Windows was a bit of a pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve found a few areas where the templating and Liquid commands don&apos;t &lt;em&gt;quite&lt;/em&gt; fit, but it&apos;s been fairly straight forward. Given my preferences, I do like that Pretzel uses LESS instead of SASS. If there was a little more active development, I&apos;d heartily recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The podcast site (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.biblebyexample.com&quot;&gt;incompletly up&lt;/a&gt; as of writing this) is using the aforementioned Jekyll. When I&apos;d finally mustered enough energy to get cracking on this project, installing Ruby and Jekyll on Windows became significantly less painful. And as long as you&apos;re willing to do a little work with the setup, WSL has made it even easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I managed a little more traction and rapid progress on the latter since I was more willing to grab &lt;a href=&quot;https://mmistakes.github.io/minimal-mistakes/&quot;&gt;a theme that someone else had put together&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both projects are up on GitHub, and are being hosted using GitHub pages. Now that&apos;s been an interesting endevour… particularly getting the domains squared away. The next step for both sites will be to get them behind &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;Cloudflare &lt;/a&gt; for some CDN goodness and HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll write a little more about each project individually, and some &amp;quot;thinking out loud&amp;quot; type posts over the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASP-Ajaxed 2.1.1: Finding my feet</title>
      <link>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/ASP-Ajaxed-2.1.1_-Finding-my-feet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 09:53:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/ASP-Ajaxed-2.1.1_-Finding-my-feet.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Woot! &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/downloads/detail?name=asp-ajaxed_v2.1.1.zip&quot;&gt;ASP Ajaxed 2.1.1&lt;/a&gt; is up. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned in an &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html&quot;&gt;earlier post&lt;/a&gt;, I took over the ASP Ajaxed project in the hopes of keeping it alive. I&apos;m still orienting myself to how Google Code hosts projects, and I&apos;m still trying to figure out just how I&apos;m going to go about running this particular project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things I found when converting the source control from svn to hg was that there were some bug fixes that were not in the posted 2.1 release. I added a couple of fixes of my own, and a new feature - a SHA256() hashing function - and published &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/downloads/detail?name=asp-ajaxed_v2.1.1.zip&quot;&gt;version 2.1.1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully soon I&apos;ll have a little more about the plans and intentions for this little project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping a good thing going</title>
      <link>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 21:53:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/Keeping-a-good-thing-going.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do a lot of Classic ASP/VBScript programming - It&apos;s what my bread-winning project is built in, it&apos;s what my side projects are built in, it&apos;s what Snitz Forums (a FLOSS project I help with) is written in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things that has made my life a little easier is a neat little ASP/VBScript framework over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/&quot;&gt;https://code.google.com/p/asp-ajaxed/&lt;/a&gt;. I&apos;ve integrated it into the LMS I built for work, and a few other work-related projects. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the owner passed away and the project has slowly faded away. Recently the main site disappeared... Not wanting to see a good code base go to waste, I&apos;ve taken ownership of the project (with the blessing of one of the remaining project members).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m not sure where I&apos;m going to begin in getting this thing back up and running, but I do want to keep this project alive and better maintained. Look for more updates to come. 😃&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Projects, New Blog</title>
      <link>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/New-Year,-New-Projects,-New-Blog.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 21:42:00 -04:00</pubDate>
      <author>Author</author>
      <guid>//blog.anonjr.com/2013/06/New-Year,-New-Projects,-New-Blog.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well... the last part is a bit of a stretch. I&apos;ve had this account for quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was recently updating my CV over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://careers.stackoverflow.com/anonjr&quot;&gt;Stack Overflow Careers&lt;/a&gt; and it occurred to me that one thing I&apos;m really short on is publicly available projects and writing... time to fix that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to tell you that I have a plan, and can outline everything this blog will and will not be - but I&apos;d be lying. Waiting until the plan coalesced is why it&apos;s now 2013 and I&apos;m just now posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; tell you that this is not going to have a singular focus. I will most likely have a heavy focus on tech as that&apos;s where I work and play - but I will also write about religion, politics, and maybe a few things of a more personal nature. Jeff Jarvis has often spoke of the therapeutic value of blogging about health issues (and I have a few) so I may throw a few of those out there as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ll see where this goes...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>