<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
    <title>AnonJr.com</title>
    <link>http://www.anonjr.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.anonjr.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 20:43:46 -05:00</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 20:43:46 -05:00</lastBuildDate>
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Special Feed for Dev.to</title>
          <link>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00</pubDate>
          <author>Author</author>
          <guid>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in January 2017 I started following what looked like a small and promising community of programmers (and those in adjacent fields) over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt;. At the time I had the site&apos;s whole feed pumping into my Feedly list, I&apos;d commented on a few posts, and I was starting to think about either revitalizing this blog or picking some other platform for posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end I decided to try and revitalize this site, beginning with &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git.html&quot;&gt;a bit on the tech&lt;/a&gt; behind a couple of projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things I&apos;d considered at the time, and mentioned in &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&quot;&gt;Projects Projects Projects&lt;/a&gt;, is setting up a custom RSS feed for just the articles I wanted to submit at Dev.To. I plan on publishing a wide variety of articles here, and I know not all of them will be right for the community there, so I want to make sure I&apos;m filtering out the rest. I tried just running my regular RSS feed to my profile there, but it left a lot of cruft on my dashboard in the &lt;em&gt;drafts&lt;/em&gt;, and even if I deleted the drafts they would just show up again on the next refresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to this bit - I&apos;ve got a second RSS feed now with just the articles that I want to send over there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the front matter I have a &lt;code&gt;repost&lt;/code&gt; variable like so:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally I was going to set up a &amp;quot;to-dev.to&amp;quot; tag, and go that way, but that didn&apos;t seem useful for the people who were visiting my site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there&apos;s now a &lt;code&gt;todev.to.xml&lt;/code&gt; that filters through the posts for just those that I want to republish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
layout: nil
---
&amp;lt;?xml version=&amp;quot;1.0&amp;quot;?&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;rss version=&amp;quot;2.0&amp;quot; xmlns:atom=&amp;quot;https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;AnonJr.com&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;link&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;atom:link href=&amp;quot;http://www.anonjr.com/rss.xml&amp;quot; rel=&amp;quot;self&amp;quot; type=&amp;quot;application/rss+xml&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;language&amp;gt;en-us&amp;lt;/language&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;Sun, 04 Nov 2018 20:43:46 -05:00&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;lastBuildDate&amp;gt;Sun, 04 Nov 2018 20:43:46 -05:00&amp;lt;/lastBuildDate&amp;gt;
    
      
        &amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Special Feed for Dev.to&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;link&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;Sun, 04 Nov 2018 22:30:00 -05:00&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;author&amp;gt;Author&amp;lt;/author&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;guid&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Special-Feed-for-Dev.to.html&amp;lt;/guid&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;---
title: &amp;amp;quot;Special Feed for Dev.to&amp;amp;quot;
date: 2018-11-04 22:30:00 -0500
author: AnonJr
layout: post
comments: true
repost: &amp;amp;quot;dev.to&amp;amp;quot;
tags:
- meta
- programming
---

Back in January 2017 I started following what looked like a small and promising community of programmers (and those in adjacent fields) over at [Dev.to](https://dev.to/). At the time I had the site&amp;amp;apos;s whole feed pumping into my Feedly list, I&amp;amp;apos;d commented on a few posts, and I was starting to think about either revitalizing this blog or picking some other platform for posting.

In the end I decided to try and revitalize this site, beginning with [a bit on the tech]({% post_url 2017-07-28-A-Pretzel-A-Jekyll-Some-Pages-Cranky-Git %}) behind a couple of projects.

One of the things I&amp;amp;apos;d considered at the time, and mentioned in [Projects Projects Projects]({% post_url 2018-11-02-Projects-Projects-Projects %}), is setting up a custom RSS feed for just the articles I wanted to submit at Dev.To. I plan on publishing a wide variety of articles here, and I know not all of them will be right for the community there, so I want to make sure I&amp;amp;apos;m filtering out the rest. I tried just running my regular RSS feed to my profile there, but it left a lot of cruft on my dashboard in the *drafts*, and even if I deleted the drafts they would just show up again on the next refresh.

Which brings us to this bit - I&amp;amp;apos;ve got a second RSS feed now with just the articles that I want to send over there.

In the front matter I have a `repost` variable like so:

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;title: &amp;quot;Special Feed for Dev.to&amp;quot;
date: 2018-11-04 22:30:00 -0500
author: AnonJr
layout: post
comments: true
repost: &amp;quot;dev.to&amp;quot;
tags:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meta&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;
Originally I was going to set up a &amp;amp;quot;to-dev.to&amp;amp;quot; tag, and go that way, but that didn&amp;amp;apos;t seem useful for the people who were visiting my site.

And there&amp;amp;apos;s now a `todev.to.xml` that filters through the posts for just those that I want to republish.

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;layout-nil&quot;&gt;layout: nil&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;?xml version=&amp;quot;1.0&amp;quot;?&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;rss version=&amp;quot;2.0&amp;quot; xmlns:atom=&amp;quot;https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;title&amp;gt;{{ site.title }}&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link&amp;gt;{{ site.url }}&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;atom:link href=&amp;quot;{{ site.url }}/rss.xml&amp;quot; rel=&amp;quot;self&amp;quot; type=&amp;quot;application/rss+xml&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;description&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;language&amp;gt;en-us&amp;lt;/language&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;{{ site.time | date: &amp;quot;%a, %d %b %Y %H:%M:%S %Z&amp;quot; }}&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;lastBuildDate&amp;gt;{{ site.time | date: &amp;quot;%a, %d %b %Y %H:%M:%S %Z&amp;quot; }}&amp;lt;/lastBuildDate&amp;gt;
{% for post in site.posts %}
{% if post.repost == &amp;quot;dev.to&amp;quot; %}
&amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;title&amp;gt;{{ post.title | xml_escape }}&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link&amp;gt;{{ site.url }}{{ post.url }}&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;{{ post.date | date: &amp;quot;%a, %d %b %Y %H:%M:%S %Z&amp;quot; }}&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;author&amp;gt;Author&amp;lt;/author&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;guid&amp;gt;{{ site.url }}{{ post.url }}&amp;lt;/guid&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;description&amp;gt;{{ post.content | xml_escape }}&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
{% endif %}
{% endfor %}
&amp;lt;/channel&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/rss&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;
At my next opportunity, I&amp;amp;apos;m going to try and pump it through the [Compress layout](https://github.com/penibelst/jekyll-compress-html) and see if that can get the size down without breaking anything. Though now that I think about it, I&amp;amp;apos;d have to either adapt it to work with [Pretzel](https://github.com/Code52/pretzel) or do the Pretzel-to-Jekyll conversion first.

So there&amp;amp;apos;s the short version. I&amp;amp;apos;m sure there&amp;amp;apos;s a more efficient way to do this, but I probably won&amp;amp;apos;t worry too much about it until I do the conversion to Jekyll. I don&amp;amp;apos;t plan on adding any more features before then.

(Hot damn! that makes 4 for 4 on my &amp;amp;quot;[Almost NaNoWriMo]({% post_url 2018-11-01-Almost-NaNoWriMo %})&amp;amp;quot;!)&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
      
    
      
        &amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Sabbaticals, Reflections, and Changes&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;link&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;Sat, 03 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;author&amp;gt;Author&amp;lt;/author&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;guid&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html&amp;lt;/guid&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;---
title: &amp;amp;quot;Sabbaticals, Reflections, and Changes&amp;amp;quot;
date: 2018-11-03 22:30:00 -0500
author: AnonJr
layout: post
comments: true
repost: &amp;amp;quot;dev.to&amp;amp;quot;
tags:
- burnout
- meta
---

I&amp;amp;apos;ve had a few versions of this post floating around for longer than I care to think about. What follows is something closer to what I&amp;amp;apos;d started around the same time I was working on the &amp;amp;quot;13 Years in the Valley&amp;amp;quot; retrospectives. For some reason I thought I&amp;amp;apos;d more directly stated just how bad the burnout was, but after looking back I apparently only had the conversation as fully and expressedly in my head.

So let&amp;amp;apos;s start the *reflection* part of this endevour.
&amp;amp;lt;!--more--&amp;amp;gt;
Burnout is one of those things that&amp;amp;apos;s been written about a lot lately, particularly in the tech industry. If you&amp;amp;apos;re not familiar, the Wikipedia page on [Occupational Burnout][7] is a good overview of the subject. [Dev.to](https://dev.to) also has a [couple][5] [articles][4] worth reading. While I&amp;amp;apos;ve not quite hit [Happy to be Here][2] territory, [Furiously Happy][3] certainly had some chapters that resonated.

If I&amp;amp;apos;m being completely honest, the warning signs were there in 2014. I may even get to some of that in a resumed rendition of retrospectives. In January 2016 I reached a point where I was at least willing to admit something was deeply wrong and find out just where I was at. So I took the [Maslach Burnout Inventory][6] and found the following results looking back at me:

{% picture &amp;amp;quot;/img/2018-11-03-MBIResults.png&amp;amp;quot; &amp;amp;quot;pure-img&amp;amp;quot; %}
&amp;amp;amp;hellip;ouch.
{% endpicture %}

I tried to work within the system, I tried counseling, and in the end it just wasn&amp;amp;apos;t getting better. In an ideal world I would have taken more regular time off, and I would have advocated for a more balanced life for myself, and recognized when the work environment was no longer healthy.

That would have been good then, so what to do now?

I remember a long time ago reading about how [we should all take sabbaticals][1]. At the time I read Joel&amp;amp;apos;s post I didn&amp;amp;apos;t really take it to heart. I&amp;amp;apos;d just finished college, and was still only months into my brand new job. The idea that I could be so tired and run down that an extended time away was needed &amp;amp;amp;hellip; I just couldn&amp;amp;apos;t comprehend it.

Now I get it. *Time to take a sabbatical.* December 15, 2017 I stepped down from full-time work and moved to a per-diem teaching position. The end of 14 years full-time work at Cape Fear Valley. Teaching was a nice way to keep up professionally, and get myself out of the house from time to time. Unfortunately, it was also still too much. So in June I quit completely.

To get ready for the sabbatical, in September 2017 I started working part-time at the local Music and Arts. I added the earnings to my current savings and pumped up what I was terming my &amp;amp;quot;sabbatical fund&amp;amp;quot;.

Knowing that given my energy levels were what they were, I kept the job to make sure I&amp;amp;apos;d get out of the house and actually engage in the time honored tradition of verbal communication with actual humans.

{% picture &amp;amp;quot;/img/2018-11-03_JabbaRelaxing.jpg&amp;amp;quot; &amp;amp;quot;pure-img&amp;amp;quot; %}
Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.
{% endpicture %}

This is where the *changes* part was supposed to go, but I&amp;amp;apos;ve run out of steam. Definitely to be finished before the month is up.

[1]: https://www.joelonsoftware.com/2000/03/18/more-on-sabbaticals/
[2]: https://www.popehat.com/2015/05/21/happy-to-be-here/
[3]: http://thebloggess.com/furiously-happy/
[4]: https://dev.to/wolfemurray/burnout-8hk
[5]: https://dev.to/mary_grace/burnout-what-happens-when-you-take-on-too-much-74d
[6]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maslach_Burnout_Inventory
[7]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Occupational_burnout&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
      
    
      
        &amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Projects Projects Projects&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;link&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;Fri, 02 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;author&amp;gt;Author&amp;lt;/author&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;guid&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html&amp;lt;/guid&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;---
title: &amp;amp;quot;Projects Projects Projects&amp;amp;quot;
date: 2018-11-02 22:30:00 -0500
author: AnonJr
layout: post
comments: true
repost: &amp;amp;quot;dev.to&amp;amp;quot;
tags:
- NaNoWriMo
- programming
- projects
- asp-ajaxed
- coffeecraft.us
- d20-Project
- bible-by-example
---

In [yesterday&amp;amp;apos;s post]({% post_url 2018-11-01-Almost-NaNoWriMo %}) I mentioned my goals for the coming month, and one was going through the various projects and giving a bit of a status report on them. Today&amp;amp;apos;s going to be a bit of a high-level overview, and the next few posts will dig a little deeper into each project.
&amp;amp;lt;!--more--&amp;amp;gt;
In no particular order, here we go:

## CoffeeCraft.us
This project is at the forefront of my mind - in no small part because it&amp;amp;apos;s one of the most recent to be started.

I&amp;amp;apos;ve got a small survival Minecraft server going at home that my sister, her husband, and I have been playing on. Inspired by [HermitCraft](http://hermitcraft.com/), we&amp;amp;apos;ve fired up a fresh world for &amp;amp;quot;Season 00&amp;amp;quot; so we can get used to working together in a way that works better for making videos and live streaming - which we all plan on starting.

The domain registered, I&amp;amp;apos;ve started in on building the website, and there&amp;amp;apos;s a few other bits in the works.

## Bible By Example
This is a bible study podcast that I&amp;amp;apos;ve been working on off-and-on for nearly a year. It&amp;amp;apos;s  been long past time to get this in gear&amp;amp;amp;helip; A decent enough first run of the website is together, and I&amp;amp;apos;m not entirely sure what&amp;amp;apos;s left to do to be ready to launch. Getting a handle on this will definitely be a part of this month&amp;amp;apos;s agenda.

## AnonJr.com
Yup, this site. I&amp;amp;apos;ve got a few things planned - from migrating from Pretzel to Jekyl, to getting a dedicated feed for the articles I want to republish on [Dev.to](https://dev.to/). I&amp;amp;apos;d also like to tighten up some style/design bits while I&amp;amp;apos;m at it.

The end goal is to make this the central hub for everything I&amp;amp;apos;m doing, and having various tags for the individual projects or subjects for those that don&amp;amp;apos;t want *everything*.

## Wayward Son Developers
This was a site I&amp;amp;apos;d put together long ago when I&amp;amp;apos;d started building sites for some friends and acquaintances, and I figured I&amp;amp;apos;d rather do it under a &amp;amp;quot;company&amp;amp;quot; than under my own name. At the time was considering doing some contract site building.

If nothing else, I&amp;amp;apos;d like to get it to the place where it serves two purposes: a showcase of what I can do for prospective employers, and a home for my programming related posts.

## D20 Project
This is an older project that I&amp;amp;apos;d started somewhere in 2014-ish and stalled out. Basically while playing a D&amp;amp;amp;amp;D campaign set in Eberron, I started wondering what it would look like if the traditional D&amp;amp;amp;amp;D setting had grown to a more modern-like world (as opposed to stalling in a Renaissance-esque world like Eberron). So I started working on a campaign setting with my sister and her husband to build just that.

The plan was to build on top of the OGL 3.5e material, and maybe make some tweaks to fit the world we were building and fix a few gripes we&amp;amp;apos;d all had at our various settings. We had some basic character building done, and were starting in on the next steps when everything kinda stalled out. Long story for another day.

## ASP-Ajaxed
Right before the burnout started kicking in hard and impacting my ability to function, I&amp;amp;apos;d offered to take over ASP-Ajaxed - a framework for Classic ASP projects. While I&amp;amp;apos;m not doing much Classic ASP work now, and I&amp;amp;apos;m not sure I&amp;amp;apos;m going to continue down that road, I&amp;amp;apos;d like to get a better project site going and tidy up a few things. As it sits now it&amp;amp;apos;s still fairly solid for those poor souls who still need to work with Classic ASP.

## Some other game streaming
I&amp;amp;apos;d like to get at least one or two more game streams going, just because I&amp;amp;apos;d like to diversify my podcasts. I worry that specializing in just Minecraft might leave me hanging if it ever drops in popularity. (though I don&amp;amp;apos;t see that happening for some time)

I&amp;amp;apos;ve considered doing a World of Tanks stream on Saturdays, and calling it &amp;amp;quot;The 48%&amp;amp;quot; (inside joke for the stat obsessed), though I worry that the game is falling and might not be around in any big way in the near future - and more important than that, I just haven&amp;amp;apos;t been having as much fun with the game lately.

I&amp;amp;apos;ve also considered doing Fallout or something like it just because I&amp;amp;apos;m a bit of an antisocial gamer. :)

## Wrapping it up
I really feel like I&amp;amp;apos;ve forgotten something, but at this hour that&amp;amp;apos;s not surprising. Tomorrow I&amp;amp;apos;ll pick one and do a bit of a deeper look at where it&amp;amp;apos;s at and what needs to happen. From there the goal is to start making actual progress and to focus the posts on status updates and/or do some thinking out loud type stuff.&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
      
    
      
        &amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Almost NaNoWriMo&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;link&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&amp;lt;/link&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt;Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00&amp;lt;/pubDate&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;author&amp;gt;Author&amp;lt;/author&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;guid&amp;gt;http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&amp;lt;/guid&amp;gt;
          &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;---
title: &amp;amp;quot;Almost NaNoWriMo&amp;amp;quot;
date: 2018-11-01 22:30:00 -0500
author: AnonJr
layout: post
comments: true
repost: &amp;amp;quot;dev.to&amp;amp;quot;
tags:
- meta
- NaNoWriMo
---

It seems a little ridiculous to tag this &amp;amp;quot;NaNoWriMo&amp;amp;quot;, but I&amp;amp;apos;m not really sure what to call it. I&amp;amp;apos;ve had a few posts in draft for longer than I care to mention, and while the desire has been there the energy has been lacking&amp;amp;amp;hellip; most likely to be the subject of some upcoming posts.

For those who don&amp;amp;apos;t know, [NaNoWriMo](https://nanowrimo.org/) is short for National Novel Writing Month. The idea being that you just start writing at the start of November, and work at a steady pace to have a completed work by the end of the month. Just writing, edit later. It&amp;amp;apos;s a really nice idea for helping those of us who just need a little push to get started.
&amp;amp;lt;!--more--&amp;amp;gt;
I&amp;amp;apos;ve gone through the motions of starting a novel a couple of times, and unfortunately never actually followed through. My intent had been to actually participate this year and produce one of the two novels that&amp;amp;apos;s been kicking around in the back of my mind for quite some time. Life being what it&amp;amp;apos;s been, I just wasn&amp;amp;apos;t ready to start and didn&amp;amp;apos;t want to feel behind this early on.

So - new objective. Blogging has been another writing activity that I&amp;amp;apos;ve long intended to do, but never seem to actually make happen. For the month of November my goal is to get at least one post out a day. By the end of November I&amp;amp;apos;ll work out a more reasonable posting schedule. The hope is that once I get started, maintaining momentum will be a lot easier.

Look for some updates on old projects, some &amp;amp;quot;talking out loud&amp;amp;quot; type planning on upcoming projects, and a few other things.

Quite frankly I feel like an athlete who&amp;amp;apos;s been on a long recovery finally getting back into training. Now that I think about it, that&amp;amp;apos;s probably a more apt analogy than I&amp;amp;apos;m ready to admit to.&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  &amp;lt;/channel&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/rss&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At my next opportunity, I&apos;m going to try and pump it through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/penibelst/jekyll-compress-html&quot;&gt;Compress layout&lt;/a&gt; and see if that can get the size down without breaking anything. Though now that I think about it, I&apos;d have to either adapt it to work with &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Code52/pretzel&quot;&gt;Pretzel&lt;/a&gt; or do the Pretzel-to-Jekyll conversion first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there&apos;s the short version. I&apos;m sure there&apos;s a more efficient way to do this, but I probably won&apos;t worry too much about it until I do the conversion to Jekyll. I don&apos;t plan on adding any more features before then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Hot damn! that makes 4 for 4 on my &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;Almost NaNoWriMo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;!)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Sabbaticals, Reflections, and Changes</title>
          <link>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
          <author>Author</author>
          <guid>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Sabbaticals-Reflections-and-Changes.html</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve had a few versions of this post floating around for longer than I care to think about. What follows is something closer to what I&apos;d started around the same time I was working on the &amp;quot;13 Years in the Valley&amp;quot; retrospectives. For some reason I thought I&apos;d more directly stated just how bad the burnout was, but after looking back I apparently only had the conversation as fully and expressedly in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let&apos;s start the &lt;em&gt;reflection&lt;/em&gt; part of this endevour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burnout is one of those things that&apos;s been written about a lot lately, particularly in the tech industry. If you&apos;re not familiar, the Wikipedia page on &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Occupational_burnout&quot;&gt;Occupational Burnout&lt;/a&gt; is a good overview of the subject. &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt; also has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/mary_grace/burnout-what-happens-when-you-take-on-too-much-74d&quot;&gt;couple&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/wolfemurray/burnout-8hk&quot;&gt;articles&lt;/a&gt; worth reading. While I&apos;ve not quite hit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.popehat.com/2015/05/21/happy-to-be-here/&quot;&gt;Happy to be Here&lt;/a&gt; territory, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thebloggess.com/furiously-happy/&quot;&gt;Furiously Happy&lt;/a&gt; certainly had some chapters that resonated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I&apos;m being completely honest, the warning signs were there in 2014. I may even get to some of that in a resumed rendition of retrospectives. In January 2016 I reached a point where I was at least willing to admit something was deeply wrong and find out just where I was at. So I took the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maslach_Burnout_Inventory&quot;&gt;Maslach Burnout Inventory&lt;/a&gt; and found the following results looking back at me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-03-MBIResults.png&quot; title=&quot;&amp;hellip;ouch.&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;hellip;ouch.&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
&amp;hellip;ouch.
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to work within the system, I tried counseling, and in the end it just wasn&apos;t getting better. In an ideal world I would have taken more regular time off, and I would have advocated for a more balanced life for myself, and recognized when the work environment was no longer healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That would have been good then, so what to do now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember a long time ago reading about how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.joelonsoftware.com/2000/03/18/more-on-sabbaticals/&quot;&gt;we should all take sabbaticals&lt;/a&gt;. At the time I read Joel&apos;s post I didn&apos;t really take it to heart. I&apos;d just finished college, and was still only months into my brand new job. The idea that I could be so tired and run down that an extended time away was needed … I just couldn&apos;t comprehend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I get it. &lt;em&gt;Time to take a sabbatical.&lt;/em&gt; December 15, 2017 I stepped down from full-time work and moved to a per-diem teaching position. The end of 14 years full-time work at Cape Fear Valley. Teaching was a nice way to keep up professionally, and get myself out of the house from time to time. Unfortunately, it was also still too much. So in June I quit completely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get ready for the sabbatical, in September 2017 I started working part-time at the local Music and Arts. I added the earnings to my current savings and pumped up what I was terming my &amp;quot;sabbatical fund&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing that given my energy levels were what they were, I kept the job to make sure I&apos;d get out of the house and actually engage in the time honored tradition of verbal communication with actual humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
&lt;img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/2018-11-03_JabbaRelaxing.jpg&quot; title=&quot;Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.&quot; alt=&quot;Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.&quot; class=&quot;pure-img&quot;/&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;
Jabba, illustrating my energy levels.
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where the &lt;em&gt;changes&lt;/em&gt; part was supposed to go, but I&apos;ve run out of steam. Definitely to be finished before the month is up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Projects Projects Projects</title>
          <link>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
          <author>Author</author>
          <guid>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Projects-Projects-Projects.html</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html&quot;&gt;yesterday&apos;s post&lt;/a&gt; I mentioned my goals for the coming month, and one was going through the various projects and giving a bit of a status report on them. Today&apos;s going to be a bit of a high-level overview, and the next few posts will dig a little deeper into each project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In no particular order, here we go:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;coffeecraft.us&quot;&gt;CoffeeCraft.us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project is at the forefront of my mind - in no small part because it&apos;s one of the most recent to be started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve got a small survival Minecraft server going at home that my sister, her husband, and I have been playing on. Inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;http://hermitcraft.com/&quot;&gt;HermitCraft&lt;/a&gt;, we&apos;ve fired up a fresh world for &amp;quot;Season 00&amp;quot; so we can get used to working together in a way that works better for making videos and live streaming - which we all plan on starting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The domain registered, I&apos;ve started in on building the website, and there&apos;s a few other bits in the works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;bible-by-example&quot;&gt;Bible By Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a bible study podcast that I&apos;ve been working on off-and-on for nearly a year. It&apos;s  been long past time to get this in gear&amp;amp;helip; A decent enough first run of the website is together, and I&apos;m not entirely sure what&apos;s left to do to be ready to launch. Getting a handle on this will definitely be a part of this month&apos;s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;anonjr.com&quot;&gt;AnonJr.com&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yup, this site. I&apos;ve got a few things planned - from migrating from Pretzel to Jekyl, to getting a dedicated feed for the articles I want to republish on &lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.to/&quot;&gt;Dev.to&lt;/a&gt;. I&apos;d also like to tighten up some style/design bits while I&apos;m at it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The end goal is to make this the central hub for everything I&apos;m doing, and having various tags for the individual projects or subjects for those that don&apos;t want &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;wayward-son-developers&quot;&gt;Wayward Son Developers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a site I&apos;d put together long ago when I&apos;d started building sites for some friends and acquaintances, and I figured I&apos;d rather do it under a &amp;quot;company&amp;quot; than under my own name. At the time was considering doing some contract site building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If nothing else, I&apos;d like to get it to the place where it serves two purposes: a showcase of what I can do for prospective employers, and a home for my programming related posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;d20-project&quot;&gt;D20 Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an older project that I&apos;d started somewhere in 2014-ish and stalled out. Basically while playing a D&amp;amp;D campaign set in Eberron, I started wondering what it would look like if the traditional D&amp;amp;D setting had grown to a more modern-like world (as opposed to stalling in a Renaissance-esque world like Eberron). So I started working on a campaign setting with my sister and her husband to build just that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan was to build on top of the OGL 3.5e material, and maybe make some tweaks to fit the world we were building and fix a few gripes we&apos;d all had at our various settings. We had some basic character building done, and were starting in on the next steps when everything kinda stalled out. Long story for another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;asp-ajaxed&quot;&gt;ASP-Ajaxed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right before the burnout started kicking in hard and impacting my ability to function, I&apos;d offered to take over ASP-Ajaxed - a framework for Classic ASP projects. While I&apos;m not doing much Classic ASP work now, and I&apos;m not sure I&apos;m going to continue down that road, I&apos;d like to get a better project site going and tidy up a few things. As it sits now it&apos;s still fairly solid for those poor souls who still need to work with Classic ASP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-other-game-streaming&quot;&gt;Some other game streaming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d like to get at least one or two more game streams going, just because I&apos;d like to diversify my podcasts. I worry that specializing in just Minecraft might leave me hanging if it ever drops in popularity. (though I don&apos;t see that happening for some time)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve considered doing a World of Tanks stream on Saturdays, and calling it &amp;quot;The 48%&amp;quot; (inside joke for the stat obsessed), though I worry that the game is falling and might not be around in any big way in the near future - and more important than that, I just haven&apos;t been having as much fun with the game lately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve also considered doing Fallout or something like it just because I&apos;m a bit of an antisocial gamer. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;wrapping-it-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping it up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really feel like I&apos;ve forgotten something, but at this hour that&apos;s not surprising. Tomorrow I&apos;ll pick one and do a bit of a deeper look at where it&apos;s at and what needs to happen. From there the goal is to start making actual progress and to focus the posts on status updates and/or do some thinking out loud type stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Almost NaNoWriMo</title>
          <link>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:30:00 -04:00</pubDate>
          <author>Author</author>
          <guid>http://www.anonjr.com/2018/11/Almost-NaNoWriMo.html</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems a little ridiculous to tag this &amp;quot;NaNoWriMo&amp;quot;, but I&apos;m not really sure what to call it. I&apos;ve had a few posts in draft for longer than I care to mention, and while the desire has been there the energy has been lacking… most likely to be the subject of some upcoming posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don&apos;t know, &lt;a href=&quot;https://nanowrimo.org/&quot;&gt;NaNoWriMo&lt;/a&gt; is short for National Novel Writing Month. The idea being that you just start writing at the start of November, and work at a steady pace to have a completed work by the end of the month. Just writing, edit later. It&apos;s a really nice idea for helping those of us who just need a little push to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve gone through the motions of starting a novel a couple of times, and unfortunately never actually followed through. My intent had been to actually participate this year and produce one of the two novels that&apos;s been kicking around in the back of my mind for quite some time. Life being what it&apos;s been, I just wasn&apos;t ready to start and didn&apos;t want to feel behind this early on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So - new objective. Blogging has been another writing activity that I&apos;ve long intended to do, but never seem to actually make happen. For the month of November my goal is to get at least one post out a day. By the end of November I&apos;ll work out a more reasonable posting schedule. The hope is that once I get started, maintaining momentum will be a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for some updates on old projects, some &amp;quot;talking out loud&amp;quot; type planning on upcoming projects, and a few other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quite frankly I feel like an athlete who&apos;s been on a long recovery finally getting back into training. Now that I think about it, that&apos;s probably a more apt analogy than I&apos;m ready to admit to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>